厄尔
Hey, Earl.
你们俩已经从好莱坞回来了吗
You girls are back from Hollywood already?
一日真是三秋啊
Time sure does move fast.
我们都还没去呢
We haven't left yet.
度日真是如年啊
Time sure does move slow,
尤其是当你们像我现在这样嗨翻天的时候
especially when you are as high as I am right now.
前面有辆车正等着带我们去机场
There's a car waiting out front to take us to the airport.
世上唯一比加长礼车[城镇车]好的车
The only thing better than a town car
就是带你逃离城镇车
is a getting-out-of-town car.
而我进来是想说
And I came in to say
前门有台车在等我上
there's a car waiting for me out front,
而且不是警车哦
and it's not a police car!
我就知道你们俩没有要去洛城
I knew you two weren't going to LA.
我就知道你俩是逗我玩
I knew you were just pulling my chain.
如果我真要逗你玩[拉你发条]
You know, when I pull your chain,
你就会发出"呜污污"
you go, "Whoo-hoo-hoo."
才不会有制片厂要大老远让你们飞过去
No studio would fly you two cross-country
就为了谈一部卡洛琳损失万贯家财的电影呢
just to discuss a movie about Caroline losing all her money.
这好笑程度紧逼上次卡洛琳说
That's almost as funny as that time Caroline said
她跟卫生局举报我们餐厅一样好笑
she reported the diner to the health department.
这话提醒了我 阿憨 这里有封信
Which reminds me, Han, there's something here for you
是卫生局寄来给你的
from the health department.
阿憨 我们真的要去洛城
Han, we really are going to LA.
其实 他们已经在跟旺旺公仔谈
In fact, they're already talking to the Keebler Elf
让他在电影里出演你的角色
about playing you in my movie.
由他或者《摩登家庭》里的亚裔女儿来演
It's between him and the Asian daughter from "Modern Family."
这话的好笑程度紧逼上次麦克斯说
This is almost as funny as that time Max said
她去市政府把我登记为性犯罪者一样好笑
she registered me as a sex offender down at city hall.
阿憨 这里还有一封市政府寄给你的信
Han, there's also something here for you from city hall.
姑娘们 发生什么事了
Girls, what happened?
你们也在禁飞名单上吗
Are you on the no-fly list too?
就把六盒电池藏在自己鸡鸡边上一次
You hide a six-pack of batteries in your junk once,
就上禁飞名单一辈子了
and you're grounded for life.
我们还是走吧 别回头
Let's just go and never look back.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这不可能是我们房间
This can't be our room.
这也太爽[套]了
This is so sweet.
所以这才叫套房吗
Is that why they call it that?
阳台 阳台
Terrace! Terrace!
楼梯 楼梯
Staircase! Staircase!
天啊
Oh, my God.
赶紧趁他们发现给错房之前帮我拍照
Take a picture before they realize there's been a mistake
之后又要被丢回普通房了
and put me back in coach.
"12步戒瘾"我不可能 但12步楼梯我可以
These are the only 12 steps anyone's gonna get me to take.
换我 换我 阳台 阳台拍
Now me. Now me. Terrace. Terrace.
这景色
The view.
快帮我拍一张带风景的照片
Oh, I need to get a picture of me with the view.
这也太赞了
This is so awesome.
我们家唯一看得到的风景
Our view at home is just a painting of a view
就是邻居家里那幅风景画
in the neighbor's apartment.
小心那个扶手哦
Oops, careful of that railing.
从上个开播季开始 已有三个下岗女演员
Three out-of-work actresses "Slipped and fell"
"意外摔倒坠楼"
from there last pilot season.
一个人坠楼叫意外 三个人就成流行病了
One fall is an accident, three an epidemic.
看 我们一人有一只宠物
Ooh, look. We each get a pet.
我是劳伦斯 酒店的总经理
Well, I'm Lawrence, the hotel's general manager.
是我给你们升级了房间
I upgraded you.
你们原来的房间是两张双人皇后床的房间
You were supposed to be in a room with two queens...
如果我在就是三个皇后[受]
well, three if I was in it.
太谢谢你了 劳伦斯
Thank you so much, Lawrence.
你人真是太好了
That's really amazing of you.
但你为什么要给我们升级房间呢
But why would you upgrade us?
你是不是疯了
Are you nuts?
你这就跟问老师周末有没有作业一样
That's like asking a teacher if there's weekend homework.
我听说你来洛城参加电影会议
Well, I heard you were in LA for a movie meeting,
到时候别忘了我啊
and, well, keep me in mind.
那当然
Absolutely.
别忘了你啥
For what?
客串
A part.
我也是个演员
I'm also an actor.
而且非常多样化
I'm very versatile.
我能演同性恋爸爸 同性恋主管
I can play a gay dad, a gay executive,
同性恋牧师
a gay priest.
这还能有别种吗
Is there any other kind?
我也能演直男
I can also play straight.
你问我前妻贝丝就知道了
Just ask my ex-wife Beth.
她当初真应该起疑心的
But she really should have suspected.
哪有直男会为了香蒜酱跟她争到面红耳赤呢
We would get into such knockdowns about the pesto.
-劳伦斯 我有点迷糊了 -有啥好迷糊
- Lawrence, I'm confused. - About what?
基佬们特别在意香蒜酱
Gay guys care a lot about pesto.
你不是酒店的总经理吗
Aren't you the hotel's general manager?
是啊 当了20年了
Yep, for the last 20 years,
等我一戏成名就行啦
until I get my big break.
所以别忘了我啊
So keep me in mind.
布莱克小姐 你的行李还下落不明
Also, Ms. Black, your luggage is still lost,
就跟我四... 三十多岁时一样[性向]不明
like me in my early f... thirties.
好好享受这房间吧 全是你们的了
Enjoy the place. It's all yours.
我是劳伦斯
This is Lawrence.
这里是我们的啦
The place is all ours!
您好 得请你们离开了
Hi. You have to get out...
大概离开一小时就好
For about an hour.
去吃饭吧 马上到晚餐时间了
Go eat. It's almost dinnertime.
我会把你们名字放到餐厅的宾客名单上
I'll put your name on the list at our restaurant.
真的很抱歉
And I'm sorry about this.
但有个大牌电影明星
It's just that I have an A-list movie star
想要在这里跟人有个"临时秘密会议"
who wants to have an "impromptu private meeting" here.
类似演员"特拉沃尔塔大战按摩师"那种事吗
Is this like a Travolta masseuse kind of thing?
我说的是"大牌"好吗
I said "A-list."
劳伦斯说我们在名单上了
Lawrence said we were on a list,
为什么我们还卡在这里
so why are we still stuck out here?
不许怪我的臭衣服
And don't blame my smelly shirt,
因为坐在那里的约翰尼·德普
because Johnny Depp, who's sitting over there,
比我臭太多了
smells way worse.
你们两个怎么还坐在吧台
Why are you two still at the bar?
你们没去找克劳德说吗
Didn't you speak to Claude?
哪个臭屁基佬是他
Which snotty gay guy is he?
这酒店里不是所有人都是基
Look, not everyone in this hotel is gay.
但克劳德是我摸鸡发誓
But Claude is hands-down-my-pants
最基的一个了
the gayest.
我还想跟你道歉 让你给我个角色前
I also came to apologize for asking you for a part...
没有让你看我的过往演出短片
without showing you my reel.
跟我过来
Come with me.
喷水池那区的无线网信号好
The Wi-Fi's better by that fountain
就是被大牌黑人女星尿过的那个
that Whoopi Goldberg peed in.
麦克斯 我马上回来
I'll be right back, Max
我有预感他的短片会特别短
I have a feeling his reel is real short.
克劳德 你是克劳德吗
Ooh, Claude? Are you Claude?
我对你婴儿时期就得顶着这名字感到遗憾
I'm sorry you had to be a baby named Claude.
我在宾客名单上
I'm on the list.
-名字 -麦克斯·布莱克[特大黑]
- Name? - Max Black.
不
No.
真的 麦克斯·布莱克
Yes, Max Black.
不
Uh, no.
这就是我 卡洛琳·钱宁
Yep, that's me, Caroline Channing.
我跟她是一起来的
I'm with her. We're here together.
不
No.
兄弟 别逼我打你
Dude, don't make me hit you.
麦克斯
Max.
麦克斯·布莱克 麦克斯 过来
Max Black. Max, over here.
克劳德 她是跟我一起的
Claude, she's with me.
很好
Very good.
我先说好 我不是妓女
Just so you know, I'm not a hooker.
我知道
Oh, I know.
妓女们想穿过领班
Prostitutes don't have such a tough time
从来不会那么费劲
getting past the maitre d' here.
我叫兰迪
I'm Randy.
请坐吧
Sit?
你为什么会觉得我需要雇一个妓女
And what makes you think I would need to hire
才会有人要跟我共进晚餐呢
a hooker to have dinner with?
我没有觉得你是个寻芳客啊
Oh, I didn't think you were a john.
我以为你是皮条客
I thought you were a pimp.
-不是皮条客 -我不信
- Not a pimp. - Uh, not buying it.
除了皮条客 谁会戴这么多银戒指啊
Who else would wear five silver rings?
每个年过四十的洛城直男啊
Every straight guy in LA over 40?
不是皮条客 也不是基佬
Wow, not a pimp, not gay.
勾人上床的绝活你都使出来了啊
You're really putting it all right out there.
你肯定是从纽约来的
You have to be from New York.
不 是布鲁克林
No, Brooklyn,
纽约市那带丙肝的淫荡表妹
New York City's trashy little cousin with hep C.
妓女 丙肝
Wow, hooker, hep C.
勾人上床的绝活你也都使出来了啊
You're really putting it all out there.
我能给你买杯酒吗
Can I buy you a drink?
买套房子呢
A house?
你在这里啊
There you are.
你好 我叫卡洛琳 我...
Hi. I'm Caroline. I'm...
-要走了 -什么
- Leaving. - What?
你走吧 我刚被升级到头等舱了
Go. I just got bumped up to first.
身住洛城 享受人生
Livin' in LA and lovin' my life.
苏菲 你好吗
Hi, Sophie. How are you?
不太好
Oh, not too good.
我以为我打的是麦克斯的电话呢
Yeah, I thought I called Max's phone.
是领养中介吗
Is that the adoption agency?
你告诉他们我们喜欢那一对
Did you tell them we liked that couple
没计划生第14个小孩的夫妻吗
who didn't plan on a 14th?
不是领养中介
No, it's not the agency.
我本是打给麦克斯 没想到却得到
I called to talk to Max, but I got Caroline's
卡洛琳的"我的人生不再悲惨"播客节目
"My life doesn't suck anymore" podcast.
苏菲 麦克斯不在
Well, Sophie, Max isn't here.
她认识了一个大帅哥
She met this really cute guy...
麦克斯已经滚到床单了
Max already got laid!
这就是为什么我爱洛城
That's why I love LA.
想当年 日落大道上上下下我称王
Hey, way back in the day, I was all up and down the Strip.
如今楼梯还能上上下下就偷笑
Now I'm excited if I get up and down the step.
苏菲 麦克斯昨晚的确没回房间
Sophie, Max didn't come home last night,
但我们不能确定她就滚到了床单啊
but we don't know that she got laid.
她大滚特滚了呢
Oh, she did...
跟一个律师
By a lawyer.
而且宣布裁定结果 太热辣
And the verdict is in: hot.
麦克斯 他的"陪审团"多大
Hey, Max, how hung was his jury?
苏菲 我得走了
Sophie, I have to go.
我们在片场有个会议
We have a meeting at the movie studio.
麦克斯 晚点再打给你
Call you later, Max.
我要听所有细节
I want details.
下面是皮包头还是皮套脖
Helmet or turtleneck?
天啊 我累死了
Oh, my God. I'm exhausted.
滚到浑身乏力吗
From all the sex?
不是 我们今早去爬山了
No, we went on a hike this morning.
洛城的约炮也太健康了吧
LA hookups are so healthy.
你运动了吗 在户外
You exercised? Outside?
你一定很喜欢这男的
Oh, you must really like this guy.
毕竟我从来没有跟律师睡...
Well, I've never had sex with a lawyer
应该说非法庭指定的律师睡过
that wasn't court-appointed.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
而且他是律师啊
And he's a lawyer?
哪种 娱乐法律师吗
What, like, an entertainment lawyer?
对啊 他客户有布莱德利·库伯 妮可·基德曼
Yep, he handles Bradley Cooper, Nicole Kidman,
乔治·克鲁尼 以及我这可撸妮
George Clooney, and... my Clooney.
早安 你的行李有消息了
Morning. Got news about your luggage.
-找到了吗 -没有
- It's here? - No.
就如同当年的我 被困在底特律了
Like a young me, it's stuck in Detroit.
佩里·泰勒办公室 我是小全
Perry Tyler's office. This is Quan.
你好
Oh, hi.
没错 当然 十分肯定
Yes, absolutely, set in stone.
我们都迫不及待了呢
We're so excited.
绝对没可能
So not happening.
但我们跟泰勒先生的见面时间
But our meeting with Mr. Tyler
是安排在二十分钟前
that was scheduled for 20 minutes ago,
这事还有可能 对吧
that's still happening, right?
当然 十分肯定 我们都迫不及待了呢
Absolutely. Set in stone. We're so excited.
-我有短信 -是我
- Ooh, I got a text. - No, it's me.
麦克斯 我真不敢相信
Max, I can't believe it.
你在期待那个律师打给你
You're hoping the lawyer calls.
我从没见过你对任何事有期待
I've never seen you hope for anything.
我本以为他会打给我
I thought he'd call.
我还挺喜欢他呢
I kind of liked him.
我为了他在白天去了户外呢
I went outside in the daytime.
妮娜在过来路上了
Nina's on her way in.
还记得吧 她就是在说故事节目上
You know, she's the executive who discovered me
发掘我的那个主管
at that storytelling show.
我比原计划慢了 你得帮我订午餐
I'm running behind, so you need to order me lunch.
我想要羽衣甘蓝色拉 外加羽衣甘蓝
I want a kale salad with a side of kale
再加一杯羽衣甘蓝奶昔
and a kale shake,
明天再给我预定个甘蓝疗程
and tomorrow better book me a kale-onic.
卡洛琳 你在干嘛
Caroline, what are you doing?
你衣服全穿错了
You're dressed all wrong.
你的故事是"公主变乞丐"
Yours is a "riches to rags" story,
你穿成这样怎么在会议上说服别人
a story we'll never sell if you go in there wearing that.
我的连裤袜在靠近胯下的部分
I have a huge hole near the crotch
破了一个大洞 这有帮助吗
in my panty hose, if that helps.
当然没有
It doesn't.
你得看起来穷困潦倒惨兮兮
You need to look broke, busted,
被社会排挤
discarded from society.
穿上她穿的衣服
Put on what she's wearing.
好吧
Fine,
只要不是让我穿你这件白痴护士披肩就行了
as long as I don't have to wear that stupid nurse cape.
这洋装你穿了挺美
That dress looks cute on you,
你们仨都美
all three of you.
对啊 你看看
I know. Ugh, look at this.
就像我第一天去上幼儿园一样
It's like my first day of kindergarten.
你好
Hi.
都过了两小时 他应该好了吧
It's been two hours. Is he maybe ready yet?
当然 我们都迫不及待了呢
Absolutely. We're so excited.
好吧 但这里随时会爆
Fine, but these are about to blow.
所以等你被胸口炸飞的纽扣弄瞎眼时
So don't come crying to me when you're blinded
可别来找我哭
by boob buttons.
你衣服里有东西扎着我了
Something in your shirt is itching me.
为什么你衣服里会有大麻烟卷
Why is there a joint in your shirt?
那还不够明显吗
I think that's obvious.
从我头发上掉的啊
It fell down from my hair.
还好是你发现 而不是运输安全局的扫兴鬼
Good thing you found it and not those TSA party poopers.
我的电话 在哪里
My phone. Where? Where it it?
我把它放在你的衬衫前袋
Oh, I put it here in your front pocket.
可以啊 我穿的时候挤得都没地方放东西了
Oh, cool, there's never room there when I wear it.
瞧 麦克斯 我就知道他会打给你
See, Max, I knew he'd call you.
-他说过他会 -他会的
- Well, he said he would. - And he will.
只是现在是苏菲
But right now, this is Sophie.
苏菲
Hi, Sophie.
领养进展如何啊
How's the adoption going?
你有找到让父母伤透心的16岁失足少女吗
Did you find a 16-year-old who really let her parents down?
厄尔 奥列格在哪里
Hey, Earl, where is Oleg right now?
他刚去厕所
He just went to the men's room
还拿着今天报纸的内衣广告
with the bra ads from today's paper.
好的 那我有45分钟
Okay, I have 45 minutes.
问题是
But the thing is,
我还是想让宝宝长得像我
I still want the baby to look like me.
你可以把假发套在任何东西上啊
Well you can put hair extensions on anything.
你是说我不该领养
Are you saying that I shouldn't adopt
应该继续努力争取怀上自己的小孩吗
and I should keep trying to have my own baby?
我得挂了 要去我们4点开始的2点会议了
Ohh, I've got go Sophie, our 4:00 2:00 meeting is on.
今天就到这吧 全
That's a wrap for today, Quan.
等等 他打算就这样走了
Wait, he's just gonna leave
完全无视我们的存在吗
and not acknowledge our existence?
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
他们对待我的方式就像知道我是谁一样
They're treating me like they know who I am.
泰勒先生
Mr. Tyler.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
Hi, Caroline Channing.
我们本来安排了见面
We were supposed to have a meeting.
简单回顾下 失去万贯家财
Quick refresher: lost my billions
尽管困难重重 但我仍拥有勇敢乐观的态度
but not my plucky can-do attitude against all odds.
我是麦克斯 我就是那"困难"
I'm Max. I'm the odds.
你是那个可悲落魄的穷鬼吃土妹
Oh, yeah, you're the sad, dejected, destitute girl.
就是我 穷鬼吃土妹
That's me, the destitute girl.
很抱歉 我今天下班了
So sorry. Today got away from me.
莱恩·墨菲可真能吹啊
Ryan Murphy can talk.
我会让我办公室明天打给你
I'll have my office call you tomorrow.
打给她
Call her?
你何不直接告诉她真相
Why don't you just tell her the truth,
你不可能打给她
that she's never gonna hear from you,
电影也不可能谈成
the movie's never gonna happen,
就像这城市的每一个男人一样
and like every other man in this town,
你满嘴谎言 满手银饰
you're full of crap and silver jewelry.
那好吧
Well, okay then.
很抱歉让你们久等了
So sorry to have kept you waiting.
全 帮她们重新安排明天的预约
Quan, set them up with another appointment tomorrow.
我这个可是白金
And this is platinum.
他真的会跟我们见面 对吗
He's really gonna meet with us, right?
当然 十分肯定 我们都迫不及待了呢
Absolutely. Set in stone. We're so excited.
所以就是没戏了
So never gonna happen.
我们现在该怎么办
What do we do now?
我上幼儿园的第一天也这么说
Well, as I said on my first day of kindergarten...
休息时间到了
it's recess.
瞧瞧你
There you are.
一大早就独自一人在酒吧喝酒
Drinking alone at a bar in the morning.
我们换衣服的时候 连性格也互换了吗
Did we switch bodies when we switched clothes?
世上某处已到喝酒点
It's 5:00 somewhere.
天啊 或许我们真换了
Oh, my God. Maybe we have.
我需要小酌几口 让自己冷静下来
I just needed a few sips to calm myself down.
很抱歉 我对制片厂那个家伙发火了
Look, I'm really sorry I lost it on that studio guy.
我猜追着他的车大声求他一点用都没有
And I guess running behind his car and begging didn't work.
哇 在洛城连道歉都如此健康
Wow, even apologizing in LA is healthy.
还有机会 妮娜现在要跟佩里见面
There's still a chance; Nina's meeting with Perry right now.
或许她能帮忙摆平这一切
Maybe she'll smooth everything over,
就像这里的所有人 企图拉"平"脸上一切皱纹
like everybody does here with their faces.
克劳德 我是卡洛琳·钱宁
Oh, Claude, hi, Caroline Channing.
劳伦斯把我的名字加进宾客名单了
Lawrence put me on the list for a table.
我是麦克斯·布莱克 你最可怕的噩梦
And I'm Max Black, your worst nightmare.
稍等
One moment.
态度这么差 怎么回事
So aggressive. What is the problem?
我猜是因为自卑吧
I'm guessing low self-esteem.
不是他 我说的是你
Not him. I'm talking about you.
我猜是因为自卑吧
I'm guessing low self-esteem.
妮娜 你好
Nina, hi.
我都不知道你跟佩里是在这里见面
I didn't realize your meeting with Perry was here.
老天 就像好莱坞的所有人都在这里
God, it's like everyone in Hollywood is here.
是啊 再一个月
Yes, for about another month.
这个地方就会空得像
Then this place will be as empty
凯拉·奈特莉家的冰箱
as Keira Knightley's refrigerator.
我刚跟佩里谈了 貌似他真的
So I just talked to Perry, and looks like
被你昨天的行为冒犯到
he was really offended by you yesterday.
我敢肯定有人对他说过更难听的话
Uh, I'm sure people have said worse things to that man.
拜托他的车牌号是"拍电影" 拽得咧
I mean, his license plate says, "Makin' Movies."
麦克斯 以你这副态度
Max, you can't have an attitude like that
在好莱坞肯定会被打入18层地狱
and not get buried in Hollywood.
妮娜
Nina.
不信问问克劳德
Just ask Claude.
派拉蒙影业公司以前可是归他管
He used to run Paramount.
所以结束了吗
It's over?
我大老远跑来这里就为了
I came all this way to be disappointed
被好莱坞一个有钱人给弄失望吗
by a rich guy in Hollywood?
我直接看凯文·哈特的电影不就好了吗
I could have just seen a Kevin Hart movie.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我最好趁酒还免费前 赶紧签单走人
I better go sign for these drinks while they're still free.
克劳德 克劳德 听着
Claude, Claude, listen,
我知道咱俩看对方都不顺眼
I know you and I haven't gotten along,
但帮个忙
but quick fave.
我得帮我朋友解决点事
I need to fix something for my friend.
我能过去跟那个人说句话吗 拜托了
Can I just go over there and talk to that guy, please?
你在名单上吗
Are you on the list?
我从未在名单上
I've never been on the list.
我可以这样一天也不累 宝贝
I can do this all day, sweetheart.
我可是同性恋伦巴舞冠军
I'm a gay rumba champion.
你好 我是你的服务员麦克斯
Hi, I'm Max. I'll be your server.
今天的例汤是"请不要毁了我朋友卡洛琳的机会
Today's soup is "Please don't ruin my friend Caroline's chance,
一切都是我的错"
it's all my fault."
当然 这是纯素 不含"奶"
And, of course, it's vegan, no dairy.
这是什么情况
What's going on here?
先生 我真的做错了
Sir, I really screwed up,
我昨天冲着你车的排烟管大喊
and as I screamed into your muffler yesterday,
现在我来恳求你的原谅
I am here to beg your forgiveness.
我不是在说你
I wasn't talking about you.
我是说 为什么我的桌子上会有面包
I meant, why is there bread on my table?
再给她一次机会吧
Give her another chance.
这是她失去万贯家财后
This is the first good thing to happen to her
第一次有好事降临
since she lost all her money,
红十字会给我们咖啡那事就先不提了[捐血]
aside from the time the Red Cross gave us coffee.
至少跟她见个面
At least meet with her,
这样你就能听听她的故事有多了不起
so you can hear how amazing her story is.
这个故事讲述的是一个人重获新生
It's a story of someone not being defined
昨日种种譬如昨日死
by all the bad things that have happened to them in the past
今日种种譬如今日生
and just moving on.
拍成电影我会买票看哦
I'd buy a ticket to that.
佩里 这是什么情况
Perry, what's happening here?
为什么你的桌子上会有面包
Why is there bread on your table?
这个姑娘试图说服我
This girl keeps trying to convince me
跟她的朋友见个面
to have a meeting with her friend.
我很久没见过有服务员这么不要脸了
I haven't seen a waitress this desperate
上一次还是昨晚莎侬·多赫提偷塞给我她的大头照
since Shannen Doherty slipped me her head shot last night.
作为你的律师
Well, as your lawyer,
我建议你 她要什么你就给什么
I recommend you give her exactly what she wants.
肯定不会后悔
You won't be sorry.
我就不后悔
I wasn't.
明天11点来找我
Come back tomorrow at 11:00.
你们可能得等一会 但我会挤时间见你们
You guys may have to wait, but I'll squeeze you in.
天啊 非常感谢
Oh, my... thank you so much.
现在我得去找我的朋友了
Now, I have to go find my friend
得赶在她不小心"意外滑倒坠楼"之前找到她
before she accidentally slips and falls off the terrace.
麦克斯 等等
Max, hold up.
你刚才的行为很酷
That was really cool of you.
就连你不打电话给我 我也不会觉得不爽了
I'm not even upset anymore that you didn't call me.
我不想一上来就追得这么紧
I didn't want to come on too strong.
我是不是不该听从大卫·斯佩德的约会建议
Should I not have taken dating advice from David Spade?
我得接个电话
Ooh, I got to take this.
当然
Of course you do.
你好
Hello?
是我
Hey, it's me.
今晚能见面吗
Can I see you tonight?
这也是大卫·斯佩德给你的建议吗
Did you get that from David Spade?
那都是跟斯塔莫斯学的 宝贝
That's all Stamos, baby.
你确定这不是又一次假安排的会面吗
And you're sure it's not another fake meeting?
因为全打给我来确认
Because Quan called me to confirm,
那反倒让我好紧张啊
and that makes me nervous.
兰迪说这次会面是来真的
Randy says the meeting's legit.
最后是
And turns out
你有了一个洛城男友
you may have an LA BF.
他不是我的男友
Um, he is not my BF.
因为"男"指的是"男孩"
Because B stands for "Boy,"
那家伙可是个爷们
And that guy is a ma-an.
你的行李有好消息了
Good news about your luggage.
像年轻的我
Like a young me,
完整到达洛杉矶
it arrived in Los Angeles in one piece...
只是多了几个洞
with a few holes in it.
这是你的 对吗
This is you, right?
当然看起来像我啦
Sure looks like me.
麦克斯 你把制服都带来啦
Max, you packed your waitress uniform?
诡异的是 我没有啊
The weird thing is, I didn't.
我猜我可能永远都逃不开那个命运的纠缠
I guess I'm never getting away from that life.
你会的 我们可是在好莱坞
Yes, you will. We're in Hollywood.
一切皆有可能
Anything can happen.
劳伦斯 你的试镜怎么样
Oh, Lawrence, how did your audition go?
没成功
I didn't get it.
或许那个角色不适合你
Oh, well, maybe it wasn't the right role for you.
是演什么啊
What was it?
一个酒店的菲律宾同性恋总经理
The Filipino gay general manager of a hotel
以前曾经是直男
who used to be straight.
下一个 下一个角色肯定行
Next one. You'll get the next one.
既然现在你的电影有得谈 可别忘了我哟
Well, now that your movie's back on, keep me in mind.
我真的是一个好演员呢
I really am a good actor.
就像现在 我在演我一点也不难过
Like right now, I'm acting like I'm not depressed.
我们出去玩吧
Let's go out.
做一些好莱坞的事情
Let's do Hollywood stuff.
去格里菲斯天文台 或看看大个小子被枪杀的地方
Let's go to the Observatory or see where Biggie got murdered.
好啊
Okay!
我找件衣服穿
Let me just grab something to wear.
天啊 我希望别是劳伦斯
Oh, my God. I hope that isn't Lawrence
又说他需要这房间空出一个小时
saying that he needs the place for an hour
因为本·阿弗莱克跟保姆来了
because Ben Affleck is here with a nanny...
裘德·洛跟保姆来了
Jude Law is here with a nanny...
加文·罗斯代尔跟保姆来了
Gavin Rossdale is here with a nanny.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我们老家也有位女士长得很像你
Hey, we've got a lady that looks like you at home.
这房间好漂漂
Wow, nice room.
苏菲 你来这里干什么
Sophie, what are you doing here?
在麦克斯说服我不要领养之后...
Well, after Max talked me into not adopting...
-我有吗 -有啊
- I did? - You did.
我在巴诺电子书店上做了点小调查
Well, I did a little research on my Barnes and Noble Nook.
你们要一本吗
Do you want one?
我猜他们现在正免费发放呢
I guess they're just giving them away right now.
不了 谢谢
No, thanks.
我更倾向用传统的方式
I prefer to lie about the books I've read
就我看过的书撒谎
the old-fashioned way.
我发现所有这些好莱坞演员
Well, it turns out all of these Hollywood actresses
都是超过40岁之后才要孩子 比如吉娜·戴维斯
that are having babies over 40, like Geena Davis,
珍·西摩尔 尼尔·帕特里克·哈里斯[同性恋男演员]
Jane Seymour, Neil Patrick Harris,
他们都找的是这里的一位治疗师
well, they're all going to this big-shot healer out here,
所以我来了
so here I am.
我跟你们待在一起 可以吧
It's cool if I stay with you, right?
-当然 -十分肯定
- Absolutely. - Set in stone.
我们都迫不及待了呢
We're so excited.